// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What are the different types of attributes?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Nominal",
      "Ordinal",
      "Spacial",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The types of a Nominal attribute depends on which of the following properties",
    answer: "Distinctness",
    options: [
      "Distinctness & order",
      "order",
      "Distinctness",
      "All the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The types of an Interval attribute depends on which of the following properties",
    answer: "All 4 properties",
    options: [
      "Distinctness & order",
      "order",
      "Distinctness",
      "All 4 properties"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The types of an Ordinal attribute depends on which of the following properties",
    answer: "Distinctness & order",
    options: [
      "Distinctness & order",
      "order",
      "Distinctness",
      "All the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Important Characteristics of structured data are",
    answer: "All the above",
    options: [
      "Generality",
      "Dimentionality",
      "Resolution",
      "All the above"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What are some examples of data quality problems",
    answer: "All the above",
    options: [
      "Noise and outlers",
      "Duplicate data",
      "Missing values",
      "All the above"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Whic model is used for encoding the categorical variables?",
    answer: "LabelEncoder",
    options: [
      "LabelEncoder",
      "OneHotEncoder",
      "CategoryEncoder",
      "All the above"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Under fitting happens due to",
    answer: "A fewer number of features",
    options: [
      "A fewer number of features",
      "Data has a high variance",
      "No use of regularization",
      "None of the mentioned"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Overfitting happens due to",
    answer: "All the above",
    options: [
      "Imbalance in data",
      "Noise in data",
      "Data has a high variance",
      "All the above"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which algorithm does not require feature scaling?",
    answer: "None",
    options: [
      "Naive Bayes",
      "Decision Tree",
      "C.B. Decision Tree",
      "None"
    ]
  },

];